<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My City!</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="cancel">Start Over</string>

    <string name="EMEA">EMEA</string>
    <string name="AMER">AMERICAS</string>
    <string name="ASIA">ASIA</string>
    <string name="OCEANIA">OCEANIA</string>

    <string name="LONDON">LONDON</string>
    <string name="britishMuseum">The British Museum</string>
    <string name="britishMuseumDescription">The British Museum is a world-renowned institution showcasing a vast collection of art and artifacts from different cultures.</string>
    <string name="towerOfLondon">Tower of London</string>
    <string name="towerOfLondonDescription">The Tower of London is a historic castle located on the River Thames, known for its role in British history.</string>
    <string name="buckinghamPalace">Buckingham Palace</string>
    <string name="buckinghamPalaceDescription">Buckingham Palace, the official residence of the British monarch, is an iconic symbol of the United Kingdom.</string>



    <string name="NEW_DELHI">NEW DELHI</string>
    <string name="indiaGate">India Gate</string>
    <string name="indiaGateDescription">India Gate is a war memorial and an iconic landmark, honoring the soldiers who sacrificed their lives in World War I.</string>
    <string name="lotusTemple">The Lotus Temple</string>
    <string name="lotusTempleDescription">The Lotus Temple, with its distinctive lotus-shaped architecture, is a Bahá\'í House of Worship and a symbol of peace.</string>
    <string name="qutubMinar">Qutub Minar</string>
    <string name="qutubMinarDescription">Qutub Minar is a UNESCO World Heritage Site, featuring a towering minaret and historical complex.</string>
    <string name="humayunTomb">Humayuns Tomb</string>
    <string name="humayunTombDescription">Humayun\'s Tomb is a majestic Mughal mausoleum surrounded by lush gardens.</string>
    <string name="redFort">Red Fort</string>
    <string name="redFortDescription">The Red Fort, a UNESCO World Heritage Site, is an imposing fort complex with significant historical importance.</string>
    <string name="chandniChowk">Chandni Chowk:</string>
    <string name="chandniChowkDescription">Chandni Chowk is a bustling market in Old Delhi, offering a glimpse into the city\'s vibrant street life and culture.</string>
    <string name="akshardhamTemple">Akshardham Temple</string>
    <string name="akshardhamTempleDescription">Akshardham Temple is a stunning Hindu temple complex known for its intricate architecture and spiritual significance.</string>
    <string name="handloomMuseum">National Handicrafts and Handlooms Museum</string>
    <string name="handloomMuseumDescription">National Handicrafts and Handlooms Museum showcases the rich cultural heritage of India through traditional crafts and textiles.</string>

    <string name="NEW_YORK">New York</string>
    <string name="centralPark">Central Park</string>
    <string name="centralParkDescription">Central Park is a vast urban park in the heart of Manhattan, offering a peaceful escape and recreational activities.</string>
    <string name="timesSquare">Times Square</string>
    <string name="timesSquareDescription">Times Square is a bustling commercial and entertainment hub, famous for its vibrant lights and Broadway theaters.</string>
    <string name="statueOfLiberty">Statue of Liberty</string>
    <string name="statueOfLibertyDescription">The Statue of Liberty is an iconic symbol of freedom and democracy, welcoming visitors to New York Harbor.</string>



    <string name="SYDNEY">SYDNEY</string>
    <string name="sydneyOperaHouse">The Sydney Opera House</string>
    <string name="sydneyOperaHouseDescription">The Sydney Opera House is an architectural marvel and a world-renowned performing arts venue.</string>
    <string name="tarongaZoo">Taronga Zoo</string>
    <string name="tarongaZooDescription">Taronga Zoo is a popular wildlife attraction with breathtaking views of Sydney Harbor and a diverse range of animals.</string>
    <string name="royalBotanicGarden">Royal Botanic Garden</string>
    <string name="royalBotanicGardenDescription">The Royal Botanic Garden is a tranquil oasis in the heart of Sydney, showcasing a vast collection of plants from around the world.</string>

</resources>